#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ chrisbeckmarketing (LinkedIn) www.sciowa.org (Company)

Top Skills

B2B Marketing Strategy Presentations Marketing Campaigns

# Chris Beck

Sr. Account Director and New Business Development at Two Rivers Marketing

Des Moines Metropolitan Area

### Summary

An experienced B2B/B2C marketing professional with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing, public relations, and advertising industries. Skilled in integrated marketing strategy, brand development/management, digital marketing/advertising, content marketing, public relations/media relations, event management, video development, and channel marketing. Knowledge of animal health, electrical wiring systems, audiovisual, manufacturing, construction materials, insurance, financial investment, banking, mining, and wastewater industries. Strong marketing professional with a Bachelor of Arts focused in Public Relations and Theatre from Coe College.

#### Experience

Two Rivers Marketing 13 years 1 month

New Business Development April 2023 - Present (1 year 11 months) Des Moines, Iowa, United States

Drive growth and expansion of the agency's client base. Responsible for identifying, pursuing, and securing new and organic business opportunities that align with the company's strategic goals.

Sr. Account Director
February 2022 - Present (3 years 1 month)
United States

**Account Director** 

June 2016 - February 2022 (5 years 9 months)

Client lead to provide strategic and tactical business-to-business (B2B) marketing guidance for a variety of companies in various industries. These include animal health, electrical wiring systems, audio visual, construction

materials, banking, financial services, large equipment manufacturers, and insurance services.

Lead annual planning, client relationships, team management to execute on and measure success of activities. Provide ongoing client consultation and account management leadership.

Account Supervisor
July 2014 - June 2016 (2 years)

Provide strategic and tactical business-to-business (B2B) marketing guidance for a variety of companies in various industries. These include large equipment manufacturers, industrial and municipal waste water equipment, mineral exploration products and services, and steel manufacturing.

Public Relations Supervisor and Account Service February 2012 - July 2014 (2 years 6 months)

Direct and manage public relations efforts for external business-to-business (B2B) clients. Work directly with clients on public relations strategy and PR plans to establish yearly goals. Develop strategic communication plans, facilitate brand audits and deliver on tactical elements.

Also work with editors of magazines worldwide including the UK, Australia, Africa, Latin America, Canada, and the USA, to secure editorial placement for my clients. Attend trade shows, host editors, and facilitate press conferences. Write editorial articles, case studies, press release, etc.

Science Center of Iowa
Director of Marketing
February 2010 - January 2012 (2 years)

Oversaw the direction of the marketing and messaging of the Science Center of Iowa. Strategic marketing plan development for traveling exhibits and brand marketing. Implementation of tactical plans covering multiple disciplines including: digital, public relations, media buying, event, gorrilla, grass roots.

Des Moines Radio Group Marketing Director and Internship Manager September 2006 - February 2010 (3 years 6 months)

PPG Industries
Assistant Manager, PPG Paint Store
August 2003 - February 2007 (3 years 7 months)

KB Toys Assistant Manager August 1997 - December 2000 (3 years 5 months)

## Education

Coe College

Bachelor of Arts, Public Relations and Theatre · (1999 - 2003)